f-r-e-e-games.com 2013-03-23

# Privacy Policy ~ Gifmania

**Summary** |   
---|---  
[Information NOT Collected - PII](http://www.blogger.com/blogger.g?blogID=3755045424403714543#collect) | We do not collect personally identifiable information (data collected with an intention to identify and contact a person such as name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) (hereinafter “PII”). However, the Lead Generation business does collect PII.  More information on the collection of PII can be found on clicking on the following link to Lead Generation’s [privacy policy](http://www.blogger.com/lead_web_privacy.shtml).  
[Information Collected - Non-PII](http://www.blogger.com/blogger.g?blogID=3755045424403714543#collect) | The non-personally identifiable information we collect may include as an example, IP address, browser types, operating systems, domain names, access dates and times, referring website addresses, online transactions and browsing and search activity.  
[How Used](http://www.blogger.com/blogger.g?blogID=3755045424403714543#collect) | We may use your Non-PII (“Information”) for the following general purposes: enhancement of our services, marketing, and to more effectively match advertisements and website content to your interests. Click on the link for more detailed information.  
[Sharing Your Information](http://www.blogger.com/blogger.g?blogID=3755045424403714543#sharing) | We may share your Information with third party service providers we have contracted with, ValueClick, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates, including ValueClick Media (“Value Click Entities”), third party marketing partners, business partners and our clients.   
[Your Choices](http://www.blogger.com/blogger.g?blogID=3755045424403714543#choices) | You may regulate the collection of your Information through your browser settings or use of "opt-out Cookies".  Click on the link for more detailed information.  
[Security](http://www.blogger.com/blogger.g?blogID=3755045424403714543#security) | We use reasonable and appropriate security measures to protect your data.   
[Changes](http://www.blogger.com/blogger.g?blogID=3755045424403714543#changes) | We may change the Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Website and if such changes are material, a notice of the changes will also be posted along with the revised Privacy Policy.   
Contact Us  | If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of or your dealings with us relating to this Privacy Policy, please email us at [privacy@valueclick.com](mailto:privacy@valueclick.com) or you can send correspondence to us at the following address: ValueClick Media, Privacy Officer, 30699 Russell Ranch Road, Suite 250, Westlake Village, CA 91362.  
  
**[](http://www.blogger.com/blogger.g?blogID=3755045424403714543)INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information.**   
As part of our on-going efforts to ensure the best possible experience for all recipients of ValueClick Media advertising, we may use log files, web beacons and cookies to collect data from browsers, advertiser and third party sites (“Sites”) to aggregate Information. The Information collected is used for marketing purposes, enables us to determine which advertisements perform well, allows us to more effectively match advertisements and website content to your interests, assists us in improving the operation of our services, helps us to maintain the quality of our services, enhances our services to our business partners and clients and enables us to provide general statistics to our business partners and clients regarding use of ValueClick Media’s services. 

“Log files” track actions occurring on Sites and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, click data and types of advertisements viewed. 

"Web beacons" are electronic files used to track your navigation of a website or collection of sites, the completion of transactions, submittal of applications and browsing behavior. 

"Cookies" are files (e.g. HTTP cookies) that are stored on your Internet enabled device (which includes your computer, BlackBerry or other PDA). Cookies are used to improve the experience web users have when they see web advertisements and ensure that when a web user clicks on an advertisement, they are sent to the correct click-through destination. We may use Cookies to estimate the total reach of an advertising campaign, as well as frequency of display. This allows advertisers to determine with greater accuracy the composition of the audience they reach. Cookies are also used to control the delivery of a series of advertisements to a web browser, and to limit the number of times a web browser receives any one advertisement. 

There are two classes of Cookies based on how long they remain on your system: (i) “Session Cookies” are used only during your visit to the Sites and are erased once you close your browser, and (ii) “Persistent Cookies” remain on your browser for 2 years from your last visit to the Sites and enable us to remember you on subsequent visits to the Sites and provide more relevant content to you on such Sites. 

There are many misconceptions about Cookies, some of which we will try to address in this policy. Cookies cannot erase your hard drive or otherwise damage your computer and do not tell us an e-mail address or any other PII. ValueClick Media does not and cannot use Cookies or web beacons to retrieve PII from your computer. 

A useful resource on understanding Cookies may be found at [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

**[](http://www.blogger.com/blogger.g?blogID=3755045424403714543)SHARING YOUR INFORMATION**

**Information Shared by ValueClick Media.**   
ValueClick Media will only share your Information for the limited purposes provided for in this Privacy Policy. This includes sharing Information (1) to enable third party service providers to assist or facilitate in the services we provide to our clients; (2) to comply with applicable laws and regulations or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information received by Us, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (3) to enforce our terms of use or to protect our rights ; (4) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service; (5) with other ValueClick Entities and third party marketing partners (including advertisers and publishers) for marketing purposes; (6) with vendors, administrative service providers, technology providers, and carefully selected partners for data validation, enhancement, information verification and suppression services or (7) for any other purpose for which you provide consent. We also may share Information with advertisers, publishers and other third parties for marketing purposes, but such Information does not include PII. While ValueClick Media strongly encourages clients and partners to adopt responsible approaches to online marketing, ValueClick Media is not responsible for the information practices of such clients and partners. The collection, use, and disclosure of information by clients and partners are subject to their respective privacy policies, which may differ from this Privacy Policy. 

In the event that ValueClick Media is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from you as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your Information is treated, transferred, or used. 

**Information Collected by Third Party Sites.**  
Please be aware that the websites of our advertiser clients as well as the websites on which we place advertisements or any third party websites linked to one of our sites also may collect information from you. Such information may include non-personally identifiable information through the use of Cookies and other technology and any personally identifiable information you may choose to give in registering and transacting with such website. Although we choose our business partners and clients carefully, ValueClick Media is not responsible for the privacy practices of websites operated by such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of such websites you visit to determine how they handle any information they collect from you. 

**[](http://www.blogger.com/blogger.g?blogID=3755045424403714543)YOUR CHOICES**

ValueClick Media also offers “opt-out Cookies” to block the placement of future ValueClick Media Cookies on your system for 10 years from the time you opted out. If you have multiple internet browsers or users on the same computer, you will need to perform the opt-out operation for each browser and/or user. If you or your privacy software deletes the opt-out Cookies from your computer, you will need to repeat the process. 

Please note that the above link for opt-out Cookies is only applicable to ValueClick Media and not any other ValueClick company website. Also, please note that use of the opt-out Cookies will affect our ability to provide you content and advertisements that will more effectively match your interests and may prevent us from controlling the frequency with which you may view any particular advertisement. Please report any problems related to the opt-out process to [privacy@valueclick.com](mailto:privacy@valueclick.com).

**PROCESSING AND STORING YOUR DATA**

**Data Processing.**   
The European Union ("EU") maintains strict privacy laws. These rules differ significantly from the laws of the United States of America (“US”). To reconcile these differences, the US and the EU have created a safe harbor (“Safe Harbor”) that defines mutually acceptable privacy operations. For more information see [www.export.gov/safeharbor](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor). 

By providing information to us, you acknowledge that we operate in the US and you agree to (i) permit us to transmit and use your user Information anywhere necessary, including across international boundaries, to better improve the services and transactions provided by ValueClick Media; and (ii) that such use by us shall be subject to the terms and conditions stated in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. 

**[](http://www.blogger.com/blogger.g?blogID=3755045424403714543)Network Advertising Initiative.**  
ValueClick Media is a member of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”). The NAI is a cooperative of online marketing and analytics companies committed to building consumer awareness and establishing responsible business and data management practices and standards. For more information, please visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

**[](http://www.blogger.com/blogger.g?blogID=3755045424403714543)Security.**  
ValueClick Media employs appropriate measures to ensure the security of all Information and We routinely evaluate our practices to identify security threats or opportunities for the improvement of our services. No transmission of information is guaranteed to be completely secure. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise data security. You acknowledge and agree to assume this risk when communicating with us. 

**[](http://www.blogger.com/blogger.g?blogID=3755045424403714543)CHANGES**

As the standards governing Internet privacy continue to evolve, ValueClick Media may find it appropriate or necessary to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. As a result, we reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time and shall post such changes on the Website. Our Website will state the date the Privacy Policy was last updated. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you use this Website to make sure you understand how your information will be used. If we materially change how we use your Information, we will notify via a prominent notice on the Website prior to implementing the change 

**MISCELLANEOUS**

**Children’s Privacy.**  
ValueClick Media is very sensitive to the issue of the privacy rights or children. ValueClick Media Websites and services generally are neither developed for, nor directed at, children. 

**Your Representations.**   
YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND APPLICABLE SITE TERMS AND CONDITIONS. You also agree that you have provided notice to, and obtained consent from, any third party individuals whose Information you supply to us with regard to: (a) the purposes for which such third party's Information has been collected; (b) the intended recipients or categories of recipients of the third party's Information; (c) which of the third party's data are obligatory and which data, if any, are voluntary; and (d) how the third party can access and, if necessary, rectify the data held about them. It is the express wish of the parties that the Privacy Policy and all related documents have been drawn up in the English language and that the English version of this Privacy Policy shall be the sole version used in interpreting and enforcing this Privacy Policy. C'est la volonté expresse des parties que la présente convention ainsi que les documents qui s'y rattachent soient rédigés en anglais.

**  Questions?**  
If you have any questions or complaints relating to this Privacy Policy or how we use the personal information we have about you, please contact _webmaster (at) gifmania.com._   We will endeavour to respond to you promptly.   

Nuestra política de privacidad describe como recogemos, guardamos o utilizamos la información que recabamos a través de los diferentes servicios o páginas disponibles en este sitio. Es importante que entienda que información recogemos y como la utilizamos ya que el acceso a este sitio implica la aceptación nuestra política de privacidad.

El acceso a este puede implicar la utilización de cookies. Las cookies son pequeñas cantidades de información que se almacenan en el navegador utilizado por cada usuario para que el servidor recuerde cierta información que posteriormente pueda utilizar. Esta información permite identificarle a usted como un usuario concreto y permite guardar sus preferencias personales, así como información técnica como puedan ser visitas o páginas concretas que visite.  
Aquellos usuarios que no deseen recibir cookies o quieran ser informados antes de que se almacenen en su ordenador, pueden configurar su navegador a tal efecto.

La mayor parte de los navegadores de hoy en día permiten la gestión de las cookies de 3 formas diferentes:  
1\. Las cookies no se aceptan nunca.  
2\. El navegador pregunta al usuario si se debe aceptar cada cookie.  
3\. Las cookies se aceptan siempre.

El navegador también puede incluir la posibilidad de especificar mejor qué cookies tienen que ser aceptadas y cuáles no. En concreto, el usuario puede normalmente aceptar alguna de las siguientes opciones: rechazar las cookies de determinados dominios; rechazar las cookies de terceros; aceptar cookies como no persistentes (se eliminan cuando el navegador se cierra); permitir al servidor crear cookies para un dominio diferente. Además, los navegadores pueden también permitir a los usuarios ver y borrar cookies individualmente.

Dispone de más información sobre las Cookies en: http://es.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cookie

Este sitio puede albergar también web beacons (también conocidos por web bugs). Los web beacons suelen ser pequeñas imágenes de un pixel por un pixel, visibles o invisibles colocados dentro del código fuente de las páginas web de un sitio. Los Web beacons sirven y se utilizan de una forma similar a las cookies. Además, los web beacons suelen utilizarse para medir el tráfico de usuarios que visitan una página web y poder sacar un patrón de los usuarios de un sitio.

Dispone de más información sobre los web beacons en: http://es.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_bug

En algunos casos, compartimos información sobre los visitantes de este sitio de forma anónima o agregada con terceros como puedan ser anunciantes, patrocinadores o auditores con el único fin de mejorar nuestros servicios. Todas estas tareas de procesamiento serán reguladas según las normas legales y se respetarán todos sus derechos en materia de protección de datos conforme a la regulación vigente.

Este sitio mide el tráfico con diferentes soluciones que pueden utilizar cookies o web beacons para analizar lo que sucede en nuestras páginas. Actualmente utilizamos las siguientes soluciones para la medición del tráfico de este sitio. Puede ver más información sobre la política de privacidad de cada una de las soluciones utilizadas para tal efecto: Google (Analytics): http://www.google.com/intl/es_ALL/privacypolicy.html

Este sitio también puede albergar publicidad propia, de afiliados, o de redes publicitarias. Esta publicidad se muestra mediante servidores publicitarios que también utilizan cookies para mostrar contenidos publicitarios afines a los usuarios. Cada uno de estos servidores publicitarios dispone de su propia política de privacidad, que puede ser consultada en sus propias páginas web.

Actualmente este sitio alberga publicidad principalmente de: Google Adsense: http://www.google.com/intl/es_ALL/privacypolicy.html
